{
    "subject": "resource/Abhijit_Pandya",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/United_Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "Abhijit Pandya's nationality is United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9447221159934998,
            "question": "Is Abhijit Pandya from the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875620365142822,
            "question": "What is Abhijit Pandya's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.715366780757904,
            "question": "If you met Abhijit Pandya, what would his nationality be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6864891648292542,
            "question": "In which nation was Abhijit Pandya born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6534960269927979,
            "question": "To which country does Abhijit Pandya belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5884109735488892,
            "question": "Abhijit Pandya's citizenship is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5643240213394165,
            "question": "What is the country of origin for Abhijit Pandya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44252508878707886,
            "question": "What country claims Abhijit Pandya as a citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.430082768201828,
            "question": "Where is Abhijit Pandya originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.259045273065567,
            "question": "Where does Abhijit Pandya hold citizenship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abhijit Pandya's nationality is United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3760_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Abhijit Pandya originally from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3760_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country claims Abhijit Pandya as a citizen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3760_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the country of origin for Abhijit Pandya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3760_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3760_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The context information mentions that Abhijit Pandya is a British solicitor (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3760/re-ranker-msmarco/84.txt) and was born in Edgware, which is in the UK.\n* The context information also mentions that Abhijit Pandya stood as a candidate for the UK Independence Party (UKIP), a party opposed to Britain's membership of the European Union.\n* These statements collectively support the conclusion that Abhijit Pandya's nationality is indeed United Kingdom."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Abhijit Pandya is a British solicitor, which supports the claim that his nationality is the United Kingdom."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}